export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Maths - Grade 7',
    level: 'Intermediate',
    totalQuestions: 5,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
        {
            question: "What is the result of 7 × (4 + 3) - 2?",
            choices: ["33", "35", "37", "39"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "37"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 cm and width 5 cm?",
            choices: ["40 cm²", "50 cm²", "60 cm²", "70 cm²"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "60 cm²"
          },
          {
            question: "If a number is multiplied by 5 and then divided by 3, the result is 15. What is the number?",
            choices: ["5", "10", "15", "20"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "20"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the sum of the interior angles of a triangle?",
            choices: ["90°", "180°", "270°", "360°"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "180°"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the next number in the sequence: 4, 9, 14, 19, ...?",
            choices: ["24", "25", "26", "27"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "25"
          },
          {
            question: "If a rectangle has a length of 15 cm and a width of 8 cm, what is its perimeter?",
            choices: ["38 cm", "46 cm","56 cm", "64 cm"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "56 cm"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the product of 9 and 7?",
            choices: ["63", "64", "65", "66"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "63"
          },
          {
            question: "If x = 6 and y = 4, what is the value of 3x - 2y?",
            choices: ["8", "10", "12", "14"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "14"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the next prime number after 29?",
            choices: ["31", "33", "35", "37"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "31"
          },
          {
            question: "If a clock shows 7:15 AM, how many minutes past 7 o'clock is it?",
            choices: ["10 minutes", "15 minutes", "20 minutes", "25 minutes"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "15 minutes"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the value of 3^2 + 4^2?",
            choices: ["13", "16", "25", "36"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "25"
          },
          {
            question: "What is the area of a square with side length 9 cm?",
            choices: ["72 cm²", "81cm²", "91 cm²", "111cm²"],
            type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: "81cm²"
          }
        ]
    };
  